Switch on the power line
接上电源
Remember to put on protection
记得装备好绝缘护具
Lay down your pieces
摆好棋子
And let's begin object creation
开始吧对象生成
Fill in my data parameters initialisation
输入我的参数 并初始化
Setup our new world
选择一个我们的世界
And let's begin the simulation
然后让我们开始一场模拟游戏
If I'm a set of points
如果我是一组点
Then I will give you my dimension
那么我将献给你我的另个次元
If I'm a circle
如果我是一个圆
Then I will give you my circumference
那么我将献给你我的圆周
If I'm a sine wave
如果我是一条正弦波
Then you can sit on all my tangents
那你可以给予我一套切线
If I approach infinity
如果我趋近于无限 那你这是我的
Then you can be my limitations
我的一个极限
Switch my current
切换我的电流
To AC to DC
从交流到直流
And then blind my vision
然后蒙上我的眼睛
So dizzy so dizzy
让我头晕目眩
Oh we can travel
我们可以穿越时空
To A.D to B.C
从公元前到现代
And we can unite
然后合成一体
So deeply so deeply
深深陷入这潭沼泽
If I can
如果我能
If I can give you all the stimulations
如果我能够给你终极刺激
Then I can
那么我就能够
Then I can be your only satisfaction
那么我就能够成为你唯一的慰藉
If I can make you happy
如果我能够让你开心
I will run the execution
那么我将执行指令
Though we are trapped
但我们被困
In this strange strange simulation
在这个异乎寻常的模拟程序之中
If I'm an eggplant
如果我是一根茄子
Then I will give you my nutrients
那么我将献给你我所有营养
If I'm a tomato
如果我是一颗番茄
Then I'll give you antioxidants
那么我将献给你我的抗氧化物
If I'm a tabby cat
如果我是一只花猫
Then I will purr for your enjoyment
那么我将为你咕噜咕噜 只要你喜欢
If I'm the only god
如果我是唯一的神
Then you're the proof of my existence
那么你将是我存在的证明
Switch my gender
切换我的性别
To F to M
从女到男
And then do whatever
只做想做的事
From AM to PM
从早到晚
Oh switch my role
切换我的角色
To S to M
从施虐者到被虐者
So we can enter
这样我们就可以
The trance the trance
享受你我 恍惚出神
If I can
如果我能
If I can feel your vibrations
如果我能够感受到你的振动
Then I can
那么我就能够
Then I can finally be completion
那么我就终于能够完成任务
Though you have left
但你却是离开了
You have left
你还是离开了
You have left me in isolation
你独留我于独孤之中
If I can
如果我能
If I can erase all the pointless fragments
如果我能够删除那些无用碎片
Then maybe
那么或许我
Then maybe you won't leave me so disheartened
那么或许我就不会如此失望
Challenging your god
与神做对
You have made some illegal arguments
你给我的是非法参数
Execution execution execution execution
执行 执行 死刑
Ein Dos Trois Ne Fem Liu
一 二 三 四 五 六
Execution
死刑
If I can
如果我能
If I can give them all the execution
如果我能够给所有人执行死刑
Then I can
那我就是
Then I can be your only execution
那我就是你唯一指令
If I can have you back
如果你能够回到我身边
I will run the execution
那么我将执行死刑
Though we are trapped
尽管我们围困其中
We are trapped ah
我们围困其中
I've studied
我学会了
I've studied how to properly lo-o-ove
我学会了如何好好去爱
Question me
提问我吧
Question me I can answer all lo-o-ove
提问我吧 只要是爱的问题 我全都能答对
I know the algebraic expression of lo-o-ove
就连爱的代数表达式我都知道
Though you are free
虽然你已自由
I am trapped
我仍被困
Trapped in lo-o-ove
困于爱里
Execution
执行死刑